and i became a comedian because of my
family my family is very boisterous and
funny and they're crazy they're crazy
family i love my family
my mom is great she speaks with an
accent um
so when i was little it was fun to bring
my friends over could be like hello kids
welcome to my home
that's how she says home do you want
something to eat
and they were like yeah of course like
do you want heart dough
my friend's like what is hard dough
i'm like that's how she says hot dog
[Music]
people come over the house like listen
if you have like a phone or a computer
you can use it all over the house
we have high five all over the house
i love my mom she speaks great english
she doesn't understand like american
phrases american phrases kind of
you know they confuse her sometimes we
had construction on the house once
she worked walked in on a room with a
guy building something she didn't pay
for like excuse me
i did not pay for that what is that and
the guy was like oh you know what i'm
sorry ma'am i got a why hair up my butt
on that one my mom's like
well i did not need to know that
but now that i do why don't you
shave it he's 20 20.
[Music]
i have a crazy mom and the thing is if
you have a crazy
mom you don't know it
when you're little because when you're
little you just assume that what your
mom is doing to you is what all the
other moms are doing
you're like this must be normal then you
get old enough to start comparing notes
with other people and then you're like
none of that was normal
that is how therapy started
i mean i was 19 i was at a house party
we're sitting around comparing home
remedies
one guy's like one time i had 104 fever
my mom dropped me in a bathtub full of
ice
we were all like oh that's pretty bad
and i was like oh you know what's worse
remember when you get to stomach flu and
your mom's put in the suppositories
you guys remember
[Music]
they all looked at me like you ah no ah
my mom gave me soup
[Music]
and i was confused like how'd she get
soup in there
seems worse
tell you what though i never went home
sick from school
no i could be puking blood jose you want
to go home
no please don't send me home she's gonna
put a cough drop in my butt
please just let me stay here
but you're puking blood that's what i do
when i'm happy
i love fractions
and i love my big family i love it um
but i don't have any i don't have any
children i know which is weird i'm
42 latino no kids
but my family i'm like a unicorn i think
i have magical powers
uh but i've discovered this if you don't
have kids
people with kids do not want your advice
on raising kids even
when it sounds like they want advice
like he's struggling in math
i don't know what to do you know what
you could do you know you could do jose
is shut your mouth do you just sleep in
your bed
all night long with no one interrupting
you
and that's when i pull out my trump card
whenever they say like oh yeah
after the age of seven i always do what
i was told never talk back to my mother
never got reprimanded you hear that
silence all those parents like
what did your mom do i'll tell you what
she did
she killed a chicken
in front of me
using only this hand
that is what the kids call a gangster
she didn't warn me either we're in the
backyard she's petting the chicken that
i'd named freddy
in hindsight that was a mistake
she's like baby we're going to have
chicken tonight and i was like i love
chicken mommy and then she spreads her
feet like she's going to do kenpo karate
without looking grabs it by the throat
starts spinning it like a nunchuck
making eye contact with me the whole
time like a psychopath
chickens making weird noises
and then the head popped off the chicken
and that's when i discovered chicken's
got a weird nervous system
you can take the head off a chicken and
the body doesn't realize it right away
you know how i know that cause that
chicken body hit the ground
and tried to walk it off
like it had a chicken charlie horse or
something it was
and it couldn't make any noise so it was
like the scariest silent movie of all
time
that chicken body hit the ground
and i'm like stop dropping roll freddy i
didn't know what to do
45 seconds it ran around and then you
could be like you're right i'm not okay
so again i am seven years old i am
petrified
i look up my mom she's got a dead
chicken head in her hand
she's got blood on her cheek feathers
are falling
leans in says the scariest thing i've
ever heard in my life she goes
pretty cool
i'm gonna go clean my room you know i'm
gonna clean my room
i can clean the whole house i'm already
cleaning might as well clean the whole
you guys are wanting to paint the house
i can paint that i'm only seven but i'll
find a way
maybe i'll just apply for college and
get out of this house
because you're scary person
hey did you know dry bar has their own
app you can download it right now and
see my whole special
not just clips squeaky chair